#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ravindra-yakkarnall-29727a6a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Interior Design
Interior Architecture
Concept Design

# Ravindra Yakkarnall

#### Architect

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

### Summary

Experienced Architect with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture & planning industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, Construction Drawings, Design Management, SketchUp, and Feasibility Studies. Strong arts and design professional with a G.D.Arch focused in Architecture from Academy of Architecture.

### Experience

Ensemble Infrastructure India Ltd Associate Director March 2019 - Present Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Dwp Interics Pvt, Ltd.
Associate Director
July 2017 - February 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Dwp interics
Sr. Associate Architect
February 2014 - July 2017 (3 years 6 months)

NELSON Sr. Architect April 2012 - February 2014 (1 year 11 months) mumbai, maharashtra

Ten creative studio pvt ltd Associate November 2010 - March 2012 (1 year 5 months)

Space Matrix Design Consultants Sr.Designer November 2008 - October 2010 (2 years) mumbai DSP Design Associates Pvt. Ltd. Sr. Architect October 2006 - October 2008 (2 years 1 month)

## Education

Academy of Architecture
G.D.Arch, Architecture · (1991 - 1996)